Von Tilzer / Gumm Collection
Music Division, Library of Congress
- Subject Files, 1931-1954 (Box 50-52)
  - Beverly Hills Hotel
    - Contracts (and related correspondence): Antonio & Sally DeMarco - Luigi Albolino & Susan R. Jarrell (Box-folder 50/7)
    - Minutes of board meetings, 1946-1954 (Box-folder 50/8)
    - Financial reports (Box-folder 50/9)
    - Miscellaneous (Box-folder 50/10)
  - Cabin in the Sky Production
    - Correspondence (Box-folder 50/11)
    - Contracts between H. Harold Gumm and Albert Lewis (Box-folder 50/12)
    - Contracts between H. Harold Gumm and Isabel M. Duncan, Al Goldin, Joe Goldin, & Jack Yorke (Box-folder 50/13)
    - Financial reports (Box-folder 50/14)
  - Jester Hairston
    - Correspondence (Box-folder 50/15)
    - Script for Chloé (Box-folder 50/16)
    - Script for Christopher Columbus (Box-folder 50/17)
    - Script for Her majesty the queen (Box-folder 50/18)
    - Script for Untitled synopsis for all-Negro musical (Box-folder 50/19)
    - Program for Run, little children (Box-folder 50/20)
    - Clippings (Box-folder 50/21)
  - Teddy Hale
    - Correspondence, memos (Box-folder 51/1)
    - Scripts (fragments) (Box-folder 51/2)
    - Contracts (Box-folder 51/3)
    - Financial papers (Box-folder 51/4)
    - Farm deed of Ted Lewis (Box-folder 51/5)
  - Georgette Harvey
    - Correspondence (Box-folder 51/6)
    - Contracts between Georgette Harvey and Merle Armitage Concerts, Inc. (Box-folder 51/7)
    - Contracts between Georgette Harvey and Roy Ellison (Box-folder 51/8)
    - Contracts between Georgette Harvey and H. Harold Gumm (Box-folder 51/9)
    - Contracts between Georgette Harvey and Lou Irwin, Inc. (Box-folder 51/10)
    - Contracts between Georgette Harvey and Guthrie McClintic (Box-folder 51/11)
    - Contracts between Georgette Harvey and NBC (Box-folder 51/12)
    - Contracts between Georgette Harvey and Theatre Guild, Inc. (Box-folder 51/13)
    - Contracts between Georgette Harvey and Richard Wheaton (Box-folder 51/14)
    - Real estate transactions (Box-folder 51/15)
    - Will (Box-folder 51/16)
    - Clippings (Box-folder 51/17)
    - Miscellanous (Box-folder 51/18)
  - Mann Holiner
    - Correspondence (including drafted agreements, etc.) (Box-folder 51/19)
  - Rex Ingram
    - Correspondence, (2 folders) (Box-folder 52/1-2)
    - Correspondence, financial papers regarding Emperor Jones (Box-folder 52/3)
    - Emperor Jones script (partial) (Box-folder 52/4)
    - Contracts between Rex Ingram and Columbia Artists, Inc. (Box-folder 52/5)
    - Contracts between Rex Ingram and Goldie & Gumm (Box-folder 52/6)
    - Contracts between Rex Ingram and Anna Lucasta Co. (Box-folder 52/7)
    - Litigation: Martha Salzberg vs. Rex Ingram (Box-folder 52/8)
    - Litigation: Ida Mae Hubbard vs. Rex Ingram (Box-folder 52/9)
    - Litigation: Muriel Rahn complaint to Actors' Equity Association (Box-folder 52/10)
    - Financial papers: Columbia Artists, Inc. (Box-folder 52/11)
    - Financial papers:Goldie & Gumm (Box-folder 52/12)
    - Clippings (Box-folder 52/13)
  - Duke McHale
    - Correspondence, (3 folders) (Box-folder 52/14-16)
    - Memoranda (Box-folder 52/17)
    - Contract with William Liebling (Box-folder 52/18)
    - Script (fragment) (Box-folder 52/19)
    - Clippings (Box-folder 52/20)
- Legal Papers (Box 53-63)
  Files arranged according to originator.
  - Harry Von Tilzer, 1899-1946 (Box 53)
    Contains contracts, litigation, death certificate, and last will and testament.
    - Contracts between Harry Von Tilzer and George Broadhurst (Box-folder 53/1)
    - Contracts between Harry Von Tilzer and Broadway Music Corp. (Box-folder 53/2)
    - Contracts between Harry Von Tilzer and William C. Dunn & Co. Music Publishers (for "The coldest coon in town" and "She's a perfect little lady") (Box-folder 53/3)
    - Contracts between Harry Von Tilzer and B. Feldman & Co. (Box-folder 53/4)
    - Contracts between Harry Von Tilzer and T. B. Harms & Co. (Box-folder 53/5)
    - Contracts between Harry Von Tilzer and Remick Music Corp. (Box-folder 53/6)
    - Contracts between Harry Von Tilzer and Abraham Schomer (Box-folder 53/7)
    - Contracts between Harry Von Tilzer and Shapiro, Bernstein & Co. (Box-folder 53/8)
    - Contracts between Harry Von Tilzer and Shapiro Von Tilzer Music Co. (Box-folder 53/9)
    - Contracts between Harry Von Tilzer and Southern Music Publishing, Inc. (for "Just across the river on the hill" and "When the goldenrod is waving, Annie dear) (Box-folder 53/10)
    - Contracts between Harry Von Tilzer and Joseph W. Stern & Co. (for "Win I lose") (Box-folder 53/11)
    - Contracts between Harry Von Tilzer and Jules Von Tilzer and Will U. Gumm (Box-folder 53/12)
    - Contracts between Harry Von Tilzer and Charles B. Ward Music Publishing Co. (Box-folder 53/13)
    - Litigation: Harry Von Tilzer vs Irwin Abrams (Victor Irwin) (Box-folder 53/14)
    - Litigation: Ludwig Baumann & Co. vs Harry Von Tilzer (Box-folder 53/15)
    - Death certificate (Box-folder 53/16)
    - Drafts of Last will and testament (Box-folder 53/17)
    - Last will and testament: documents regarding probate (Box-folder 53/18)
  - Estate of Harry Von Tilzer, 1927-1957 (Box 53-54)
    Contains papers generated by settling of the estate; agreements regarding Aimee V. Samuels (stepdaughter) claim; papers regarding other estates pertaining to the settlement of Harry Von Tilzer's estate.
    - Application to determine the estate tax (Box-folder 53/19)
    - Appraisal of the estate (Box-folder 53/20)
    - Final judicial settlement of H. Harold Gumm as executor (Box-folder 53/21)
    - Objections of Estelle Von Tilzer (Box-folder 53/22)
    - Proving the last will and testament of Harry Von Tilzer (Box-folder 53/23)
    - Release and discharge of executor (Box-folder 53/24)
    - Aimee V. Samuels [stepdaughter of Harry Von Tilzer]: Agreements regarding claim on Harry Von Tilzer estate (Box-folder 54/1)
    - Aimee V. Samuels [stepdaughter of Harry Von Tilzer]: Correspondence regarding claim on Harry Von Tilzer estate (Box-folder 54/2)
    - Jack and Isabel Von Tilzer: Adoption papers (Box-folder 54/3)
    - Papers regarding other estates pertaining to settlement of Harry Von Tilzer estate: Cohan, George M. [used for comparison] (Box-folder 54/4)
    - Papers regarding other estates pertaining to settlement of Harry Von Tilzer estate: Gershwin, George [used for comparison] (Box-folder 54/5)
    - Papers regarding other estates pertaining to settlement of Harry Von Tilzer estate: Goldie, William V.--Correspondence (Box-folder 54/6)
    - Papers regarding other estates pertaining to settlement of Harry Von Tilzer estate: Goldie, William V.--Death certificate, marriage license, will, etc. (Box-folder 54/7)
    - Papers regarding other estates pertaining to settlement of Harry Von Tilzer estate: Goldie, William V.--Federal tax returns, 1949-1953 (Box-folder 54/8)
    - Papers regarding other estates pertaining to settlement of Harry Von Tilzer estate: Von Tilzer, Albert (Box-folder 54/9)
    - Papers regarding other estates pertaining to settlement of Harry Von Tilzer estate: Von Tilzer, Ida (Box-folder 54/10)
    - Papers regarding other estates pertaining to settlement of Harry Von Tilzer estate: Von Tilzer, Isabel (Box-folder 54/11)
    - Papers regarding other estates pertaining to settlement of Harry Von Tilzer estate: Von Tilzer, Will (Box-folder 54/12)
    - Papers regarding other estates pertaining to settlement of Harry Von Tilzer estate: Young, Joseph [used for comparison] (Box-folder 54/13)
  - Harry Von Tilzer Music Publishing Co. (HVTMPC), 1903-1956 (Box 55-63)
    Contains organizational papers; song and show contracts (arranged alphabetically by title in two alphabets); other contracts (arranged by name of individual or organization); litigation (arranged alphabetically by name of litigant).
    - By-laws (Box-folder 55/1)
    - Minutes of board of directors (Box-folder 55/2)
    - Certificate of incorporation (Box-folder 55/3)
    - Memos regarding incorporation and other topics (Box-folder 55/4)
    - Reinstatement of incorporation (Box-folder 55/5)
    - Certificate of corporate banking (Box-folder 55/6)
    - Lease and other items (Box-folder 55/7)
    - Contracts: Songs
      - Annette; Addison Burkhardt/Arthur Behim, 1912 (Box-folder 55/8)
      - Are you half the man; James Amoroso/unknown, 1916 (Box-folder 55/9)
      - Baby doll (also known as Angel child); Harry Armstrong/William Clark, 1910 (Box-folder 55/10)
      - Baby, save your kisses for me; Fred Strasser/Frank Tinney, 1911 (Box-folder 55/11)
      - Baltimore ("Baldy Moore"); Andy Rice, 1907 (Box-folder 55/12)
      - Big Chief Dynamite; Al Piantadosi, undated (Box-folder 55/13)
      - Buzzy bee; Billy Borden/Joe Denny, 1911 (Box-folder 55/14)
      - Celia; Walter Smart/Harry Wellman, 1903 (Box-folder 55/15)
      - Chloe; Eddie Leonard/J. C. Levan, 1921 (Box-folder 55/16)
      - Cindy, you're my dream; J. B. Mullen, 1903 (Box-folder 55/17)
      - Contentment; Billy Curtis/Harry Von Tilzer, 1932 (Box-folder 55/18)
      - Cotton pickin' time in Alabama; Arthur J. Daly/Harold L. Cool, 1917 (Box-folder 55/19)
      - Country days; Albert Weiler, 1921 (Box-folder 55/20)
      - Creole jazz; Karyl Norman, 1922 (Box-folder 55/21)
      - Dearest days; Harry Truax, 1911 (Box-folder 55/22)
      - Does anybody want my fido; Garfield Kilgour/Harry Von Tilzer, 1918 (Box-folder 55/23)
      - Don't say good-bye; Dannie O'Neil, 1921 (Box-folder 55/24)
      - Dreaming of love; Harry Truax, 1911 (Box-folder 55/25)
      - Duty calls; Dr. M. Hall/C. A. Egener, 1918 (Box-folder 55/26)
      - The easiest way; Arthur Behim, 1909 (Box-folder 55/27)
      - East is east, west is west; Jack Yellen/Milton Ager, 1922 (Box-folder 55/28)
      - Everything's been done before; Eddie Leonard, 1911 (Box-folder 55/29)
      - The garden of lies; A. K. Allison/Harry Von Tilzer, 1914 (Box-folder 55/30)
      - Georgia was so different from the rest; William Davis/unknown,1912 (Box-folder 55/31)
      - Giddy-ap, Pocahontas, good-bye; Richard Howard/Harry Von Tilzer, 1918 (Box-folder 55/32)
      - The girl I left before I left; Jack Mahoney, 1908 (Box-folder 55/33)
      - Golden eyes; Don V. Harwood/Alice Lawlor, 1913 (Box-folder 55/34)
      - Grandma's Sunday dinner; Edward Maddan/Alfred J. Doyle, 1910 (Box-folder 55/35)
      - The goose step; Earl Benham/unknown, 1921 (Box-folder 55/36)
      - He was a hero in the army; Sam Landers/Phil Baker, 1919 (Box-folder 55/37)
      - Here I am; Annie Kent, 1914 (Box-folder 55/38)
      - Honeymoon; R. C. McPherson/Chris Smith, 1902 (Box-folder 55/39)
      - Hula girl (instrumental); James Europe, 1910 (Box-folder 55/40)
      - I don't count for nuffin' anymore; Marie Tyler (author of title), 1912 (Box-folder 55/41)
      - I just can't make my heart behave; unknown/Harry Von Tilzer [unsigned], [undated] (Box-folder 55/42)
      - I just made up with my darling; Dolph Singer/J. Fred Coots, 1926 (Box-folder 55/43)
      - I never knew that a girl like you; Paul Cunningham/Alfred J. Doyle, 1914 (Box-folder 55/44)
      - I should worry; L. Wolfe Gilbert, 1911 (Box-folder 55/45)
      - I want everyone to love me; unknown/Arthur E. Behim, 1911 (Box-folder 55/46)
      - I want someone to chase the blues away; unknown/Murray Bloom, 1915 (Box-folder 55/47)
      - I wish I was King Solomon; Will J. Harris, 1915 (Box-folder 55/48)
      - I wish I were you; Ballard MacDonald/Harry M. Piano, 1911 (Box-folder 55/49)
      - I'd like to know you better; Francis De Witt/Aubrey Stauffer, 1909 (Box-folder 55/50)
      - If a girl wants a boy and a boy; Checkers Von Hampton/Henry Cohen, 1909 (Box-folder 55/51)
      - If love were a yard long; Bartlett Costello/John Heinzman, 1910 (Box-folder 55/52)
      - If you don't vant her, I vant her; Lew Brown/unknown, 1911 (Box-folder 55/53)
      - I'll get you; Hal Dyson, 1922 (Box-folder 55/54)
      - I'll put the blame on Mr. Rubinstein; Eugene Platzman, 1910 (Box-folder 55/55)
      - I'm going to leave this town; Andrew B. Sterling/Elmer Bowman, 1911 (Box-folder 55/56)
      - In de evenin'; Alex Rogers/Will Marion Cook, 1910 (Box-folder 55/57)
      - In my garden of golden dreams; W. E. Browning/Alfred J. Doyle, 1910 (Box-folder 55/58)
      - In my little Honolulu cabaret; Louis Harrison/Harry Von Tilzer, 1917 (Box-folder 55/59)
      - It's going to be tough on the old men; B. Russell, A.B. Sterling/George Bennett, 1918 (Box-folder 55/60)
      - It's got to be someone I love; Will Dillon/Alfred J. Doyle, 1910 (Box-folder 55/61)
      - I've won the family over; Felix Adler, 1911 (Box-folder 55/62)
      - Jakey with the hook and ladder; Al Piantadosi, [undated] (Box-folder 55/63)
      - Just as if I didn't know; Billy Curtis, 1919 (Box-folder 55/64)
      - Just like Hennessy; Alexander Groves/unknown, 1910 (Box-folder 55/65)
      - Just like taking candy from a baby; Will J. Hart/Ed Nelson, 1917 (Box-folder 55/66)
      - Kiss for shame; Albert H. Fitz, 1904 (Box-folder 55/67)
      - Kitty Rooney; Andrew B. Sterling/Arthur E. Behim, 1910 (Box-folder 55/68)
      - Land o' love; Walter Stanton, 1919 (Box-folder 56/1)
      - Laugh with me; Albert Weiler, 1920 (Box-folder 56/2)
      - Laughing song; Billy Curtis/unknown, 1920 (Box-folder 56/3)
      - Let's see, um, um, that's right; George Whiting, 1908 (Box-folder 56/4)
      - Life; Fay Tishman/Marjorie Goetschius, 1956 (Box-folder 56/5)
      - Lize, those great big beautiful eyes; Eddie Leonard, 1911 (Box-folder 56/6)
      - Lost, a girl; Leon Bennett/unknown, 1911 (Box-folder 56/7)
      - L-O-V-E spells love; Rosetta and Vivian Duncan, 1921 (Box-folder 56/8)
      - Loving eyes; Harry Puck, Alfred Bryan, George Meyer, 1908 (Box-folder 56/9)
      - Ma belle rose; Arthur E. Behim, 1910 (Box-folder 56/10)
      - M'cool; Jim Ward/Bob Willis, 1914 (Box-folder 56/11)
      - Meet me in St. Louis, Louis; Andrew B. Sterling/unknown, [1904] (Box-folder 56/12)
      - Miserary; Woods, Frazer and Lederer, 1910 (Box-folder 56/13)
      - Moonlight in Vermont; John Blackburn/Karl Suessdorf, 1944 (Box-folder 56/14)
      - More; Arthur E. Behim, 1910 (Box-folder 56/15)
      - Mother's blues; Murray Roth/unknown, 1921 (Box-folder 56/16)
      - My Dixie dream; Earl Taylor, 1910 (Box-folder 56/17)
      - My little curly head girl; Lew Farris/Emil Valezco, Herbert Straub, 1927 (Box-folder 56/18)
      - My little dreamland Rose; C. M. Dennison/Anna Bumaer Berg, 1911 (Box-folder 56/19)
      - My Madeline; Louis Dacre, 1903 (Box-folder 56/20)
      - My sweet American rose; Alice Melville/Tom Edwards, 1917 (Box-folder 56/21)
      - The naughty Lucie bump; Edward Madden, 1910 (Box-folder 56/22)
      - The nervous knee; Garfield Kilgour/Walter Scanlan, 1918 (Box-folder 56/23)
      - Not so good, not so bad; Murray Roth/Unknown, 1921 (Box-folder 56/24)
      - Now's the time; Edward Grossmith/Ted D. Ward, 1916 (Box-folder 56/25)
      - Oh, Daddy come home; Tom Helmick/Vincent Rose, 1915 (Box-folder 56/26)
      - Oh! What I know about you; W. Raymond Walker [copyright], 1909 (Box-folder 56/27)
      - On Ragtime Bay; Bernard Grossman/Fred Watson, 1913 (Box-folder 56/28)
      - On that Mississippi shore; Billy Curtis/Harry Von Tilzer, 1919 (Box-folder 56/29)
      - On the way to Oskaloo; Billy Curtis/Unknown, 1920 (Box-folder 56/30)
      - Princeton cheer song; Charles W. Orth/W.D. Biekhan, 1911 (Box-folder 56/31)
      - Roly boly eyes; Eddie Leonard, 1919 (Box-folder 56/32)
      - The rose of my dreams; Ben Barnett/Marie Scanlon, 1913 (Box-folder 56/33)
      - Rose of my heart; Ben Bernard, 1920 (Box-folder 56/34)
      - Sardinia; Andrew B. Sterling/unknown, 1921 (Box-folder 56/35)
      - She says the cutest things; Dolph Singer, Paul Ash, Dave Dreyer, 1926 (Box-folder 56/36)
      - Sister hasn't got a chance since Mother; unknown/Harry Von Tilzer [unsigned], [undated] (Box-folder 56/37)
      - Smile; Fred Ziemer/Dewitt Bell, 1909 (Box-folder 56/38)
      - Some day little girl; Lew Brown/W. Raymond Walker, 1911 (Box-folder 56/39)
      - Somebody; Jeff T. Branen/Joe Hollander, 1911 (Box-folder 56/40)
      - Someone cares; Frank Davis/George J. Bennett, 1920 (Box-folder 56/41)
      - Star kiss; Jack McGarr/Murray Bloom, Jesse Greer, 1920 (Box-folder 56/42)
      - Telephone your Rivky, Izzie; Addison Burkhardt/Lillian Shaw, 1910 (Box-folder 56/43)
      - That woodland cabaret; Art M. Swanstrom/Leo Bennett, 1913 (Box-folder 56/44)
      - That's where I meet my girl; J. Vincent Healy, Dolph Singer/Harry Von Tilzer, 1926 (Box-folder 56/45)
      - Tina waltzes; unknown/Alberto Rizzi, 1915 (Box-folder 56/46)
      - Two little true little blue little eyes; Dave Dreyer, Dolph Singer, Jimmy Steiger, 1927 (Box-folder 56/47)
      - Underneath the chestnut tree; Alfred Bryan, 1904 (Box-folder 56/48)
      - Wandering one; Harry Mayo/Harry Von Tilzer, 1924 (Box-folder 56/49)
      - We are never too old to love; William Cahalin, Philip Moore/Harold C. O'Hare, 1916 (Box-folder 56/50)
      - When I look in the mirror; Dan Sullivan/Harry Von Tilzer, 1919 (Box-folder 56/51)
      - When I send you a picture of Berlin; Dave Dreyer, Ben Ryan, Frank Fay, 1918 (Box-folder 56/52)
      - When I'm with you; unknown/Bill Munro, 1920 (Box-folder 56/53)
      - When my baby smiles at me; Andrew B. Sterling, Ted Lewis/Bill Munro, 1938 (Box-folder 56/54)
      - When Rosa Rosano sings matse soprano; Edward Clark [unsigned], [undated] (Box-folder 56/55)
      - When you're painting my Irish home; Frank Terry, 1916 (Box-folder 56/56)
      - Whether it rains, whether it shines; Dolph Singer/Harry Von Tilzer [MPPA title registration], 1927 (Box-folder 56/57)
      - Whistle a tune; unknown/Harry Von Tilzer [unsigned], [undated] (Box-folder 56/58)
      - Whistling charms; unknown/Alberto Rizzi, 1915 (Box-folder 56/59)
      - With a far away look in her eye; Garfield Kilgour/Harry Von Tilzer, 1916 (Box-folder 56/60)
      - Won't you change your name to Reilly; Herbert W. Smith/unknown, 1910 (Box-folder 56/61)
      - Won't you say yes today; Mark E. Beam, 1911 (Box-folder 56/62)
      - The Yiddisha wedding dance; Arthur Fields/Harry Carroll, 1911 (Box-folder 56/63)
      - You are my life, my all; Alfred J. Doyle, 1907 (Box-folder 56/64)
      - You can't eat peas with a knife; Harry Von Tilzer [MPPA title registration], 1927 (Box-folder 56/65)
      - You can't take away what you gave; Arthur Terker, 1919 (Box-folder 56/66)
      - You certainly have opened my eyes; Harry David Kerr/Harry Von Tilzer, 1914 (Box-folder 56/67)
      - You're not with Billy tonight; Billy K. Wells/Al Steadman, 1913 (Box-folder 56/68)
      - Zuleika; Andrew B. Sterling, 1903 (Box-folder 56/69)
      - [Empty contract envelopes] (Box-folder 56/70)
    - Contracts: Shows
      - Heigh-Ho [previously called Insults]; Leo Donnelly and Dolph Singer/Harry Von Tilzer, Contains contract with Leo Feist (1929), copyright renewals (1956), and relevant correspondence (1956). (Box-folder 57/1)
      - Hoosier Girl; Edward P. Moran/Harry Von Tilzer, Contains an agreement between Moran, the Harry Von Tilzer estate, and HVTMPC (1947). (Box-folder 57/2)
      - Mad Love; Frances Nordstrom/Harry Von Tilzer, Agreements between Nordstrom and Harry Von Tilzer (1919, 1920) Agreement between producer Lew Fields, HVTMPC, and Harry Von Tilzer (1920) Agreement between Fields, Nordstrom, and Harry Von Tilzer (1920) Agreement between Nordstrom and HVTMPC (1920) Receipt from Edward Madden for payment for revision (Box-folder 57/3)
      - To-Day [previously called Style], Agreement between Abraham S. Schomer and Max R. Wilner (1913) Assignment of proxy by Max R. Wilner to Harry M. Wilner in Drama Producing Corporation Certificate of Incorporation of the Manuscript Producing Corporation Agreement between George Broadhurst, Harry Von Tilzer, and Max R. Wilner as stockholders of the Manuscript Producing Company, and the same three as Trustees Agreement between Max R. Wilner, Harry Von Tilzer, George Broadhurst, Harold Gumm, and the Manuscript Producing Company Agreement between George H. Broadhurst and Abraham S. Schomer and The Macaulay Company (publisher) (Box-folder 57/4)
      - You Know Me Al; Hugh Stanislaus Stange, Stannard Mears, W. Anson Hallihan/Harry Von Tilzer, Agreement between Joseph Andre Tressi (manager) and Hugh Stanislaus Stange, Stannard Mears, W. Andon Hallihan (authors) and Harry Von Tilzer (composer) (Box-folder 57/5)
    - Contracts between HVTMPC and the following:
      - American Federation of Musicians (Box-folder 57/6)
      - ASCAP (Box-folder 57/7)
      - Bornstein, Ben (Box-folder 57/8)
      - Candy Music Publishing Co. (Box-folder 57/9)
      - Cohen, Meyer (Box-folder 57/10)
      - Herman Darewski Music Publishing Co., Ltd. (Box-folder 57/11)
      - Decca Records, Inc. (Box-folder 57/12)
      - Dyson, Hal R. and William K. Wells (Box-folder 57/13)
      - Fero, James (Box-folder 57/14)
      - Fitzgerald, Dallas M. (Box-folder 57/15)
      - Hill, Gus et al (Box-folder 57/16)
      - Music Autographers' Union (Box-folder 57/17)
      - O'Day, James (Box-folder 57/18)
      - Paramount Famous Lasky Corporation (Box-folder 57/19)
      - Preston, E. D. and Arthur Wimperis (Box-folder 57/20)
      - Smith, Samuel (Box-folder 57/21)
      - Smitman, Ralph (Box-folder 57/22)
      - Sterling, Andrew B. (Box-folder 57/23)
      - Jerry Vogel Music Co., Inc. (Box-folder 57/24)
      - Von Tilzer, Albert and Harry, and Jack Louis Gumm (Box-folder 57/25)
      - Von Tilzer, Harry and Will (Box-folder 57/26)
    - Contracts between the following:
      - Broadway Music Corp. - Simon & Schuster (Box-folder 57/27)
      - Feist, Leo - Walter Donaldson (Box-folder 57/28)
      - Feist, Leo - Harry Von Tilzer (Box-folder 57/29)
      - Mills, F. A. - William S. Estrell[?] & Budd Minor[?] (Box-folder 57/30)
      - Singer, Dolph - Various vaudeville artists (Box-folder 57/31)
      - Von Tilzer, Albert - Stasny Music Corp. (Box-folder 57/32)
    - Other legal documents
      - Certificate of incorporation for Vontil Corporation (1913) (Box-folder 57/33)
      - Correspondence regarding Certificate of incorporation for Shapiro, Bernstein & Von Tilzer (Box-folder 57/34)
      - Miscellaneous forms (Box-folder 57/35)
    - Litigation: HVTMPC vs. the following:
      - Columbia Recording Corporation correspondence, 1927, 1943-1944 (Box-folder 58/1)
      - Columbia Recording Corporation releases, 1943-1944 (Box-folder 58/2)
      - Leo Feist, Inc., et al, Affidavit, Order to show just cause, etc. (Box-folder 58/3)
      - Leo Feist, Inc., et al, Complaint, depositions, etc. (Box-folder 58/4)
      - Leo Feist, Inc., et al, Arthur J. Lamb & M. Witmark & Sons (Box-folder 58/5)
      - Loew's, Inc., et al, Correspondence, music, clippings (Box-folder 58/6)
      - Loew's, Inc., et al, Interrogatories, final release, etc. (Box-folder 58/7)
      - Jerry Vogel Music Co., et al
        - General correspondence, 1937-1955, undated, (12 folders) (Box-folder 59/1-12)
        - Correspondence between HVTMPC and Goldie & Gumm, 1939-1955, undated, (3 folders) (Box-folder 59/13-15)
        - Correspondence with Harry Fox regarding royalties and synchronization rights of disputed songs, 1941-1947 (Box-folder 59/16)
        - Correspondence with Sol Leibner of Leibner & Chaikin, Accountants, 1947-1952 (Box-folder 59/17)
        - Correspondence regarding Pauline B. Story, 1938 (Box-folder 59/18)
        - Trial documents
          Arranged alphabetically by type of document.
          - Account of plaintiff (Box-folder 60/1)
          - Appeal (Box-folder 60/2)
          - Audit of Jerry Vogel Music Co. by HVTMPC, June 1947 (Box-folder 60/3)
          - Briefs from defendant (Box-folder 60/4)
          - Briefs from defendant-appellant (Box-folder 60/5)